[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Would you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Ryan, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I'm doing good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Are you happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes, I'm happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Drinking competitions, I mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes, I'd say so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Who gets more women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I've been asked this question before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "It's you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I think it's a tossup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 83, "question": "It's you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I'm sure it's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Who would be the right kind of woman for your boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "That would have to be a family-loving person that could stand having a large family, and crazy family at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What does she mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "She meant that I go on dates.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Blake Lively"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Who would you take right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Right now, Blake Lively.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Would you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Have you met her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "No, never met her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "If she's watching this, and she probably is, what would you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "I'd be like, hi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Reynolds"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Do you want to go to an island with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "She's dating Ryan Reynolds who I think he's overrated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "How much is that worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "A lot of money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "You like your bling, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Did you wake up and think Chinese -- are they the big rivals now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "You know what, it's hard to choose from a different country, because there's so many that are outstanding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Did you expect Michael Phelps to come and congratulate you, or did you understand in that moment he was like, you're the last guy he wants to talk to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "You know, he did come up and say congrats.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Not in the pool, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Not in the pool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "What kind of dedication does it take to be a gold medal winner at the Olympic Games?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "It takes a lot, a lot of early-morning practices, and going into a freezing cold pool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What is in your head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "That, this right here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What is going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Chills.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Do you feel like you are swimming for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Greatest feeling in your life when you win a gold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Big Mac"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Are you just so fit now you can go to the huge McDonald's over there, the world's biggest McDonald's, gorge yourself on Big Macs for an hour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "EX", ",", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NNP", "POS", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "After this interview I'm going to go over there and get a Big Mac.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McDonald's", "McDonald's", "Big Macs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Can you eat what you like, seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Do you feel like you're a New Yorker still?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I can't do the cold that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "You moved to Florida, what, you were 8 years old you said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Eleven.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "When he was a young guy, what kind of young boy did you try to steer him toward being as a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I tried to steer him as being an honest, fun-loving, caring individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Did he ever beat you, or did you say, you know what, when you beat me for real?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No, never, never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "As a parent, which is the more extreme?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "That's a hard question to answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Was when?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "When I was on the podium, the national anthem was being raised and they showed the JumboTron.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "You love this, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I do, I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What does it say about you when you put this in your mouth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "You know, I guess it's part of my personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Do you read this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Are you amused or bemused by the fact you have a guy pretending to be you tweeting to the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Veronica, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I'm doing good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "You're the woman who's going to break all American hearts by beating Allyson Felix, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I don't know what the future holds.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allyson Felix"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Trelawny"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "It's actually where Usain Bolt comes from as well, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Yes, indeed, Trelawny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Why are you all being created in this tiny little part of Jamaica?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "There's a lot of factors.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jamaica"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Are you a big yam eater?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I do enjoy eating yam.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "I imagine it was very competitive when you were young, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "You used to run bare foot, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Did you beat the boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "AMPBELL-BROWN: I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "When you're getting down there and you're the favorite, the pressure is on, what are you feeling in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I'm calm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jamaica", "U.S."]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "And you're able to hold off America and you're able to hold off America and all these American sprinters when it's 350 times as big as Jamaica?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Jamaica and the U.S. have a very rich tradition in the sprint and I enjoy competing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America", "Jamaica"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Do you ever quietly get it on when you're back in Chalorny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "No, no, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chalorny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do you reckon you could take him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Is he a real good guy in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "AMPBELL-BROWN: He's a very talented athlete.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "You've been seeing the swimming event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I did yesterday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Are you keen on him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "He's gorgeous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "How many times are you plan on watching the swimming this week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "A lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "What are your other favorite sports?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I love gymnastics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Are you a sporty girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Not necessarily playing sports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "MD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, I mean, the thing is, I think when you are preparing to could something like that, I think it should really be up to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "You would sing it, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Of course, I would sing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What do you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I think it's actually really exciting, you know, because it's like an all-star cast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "The opening ceremony was pretty spectacular, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What was your favorite part?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Honestly, it was the queen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, it's a campaign for sort of getting the country behind the team, as the host nation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November", "December"], "LOCATION": ["South Africa", "Taiwan", "Japan", "China", "United States"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Where are you going on tour next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I'm off now to South Africa at the end of the week, Taiwan, Japan, China, and I'm going to be back in the United States in November and December.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "How are you coping with your new-found fame in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "It's lovely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Alfie Boe, how are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I'm very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Bradley Wiggins and his sideburns, everything else, what does it feel like to be a Brit right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well, it's great for me because I know they've all been listening to the actual anthem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bradley Wiggins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Do you still work on cars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I've polished a lot of cars in my life so I try to avoid it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "When you look at the Olympic spirit, what does it mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "For me personally, I'm proud to be British.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Do you go there much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "We had a house there a while back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "What do you do that's so bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "I sometimes let my frustration run away with me when I see opera houses or the opera establishment telling artists what they can and can't do, saying what is an opera singer, what classical music is and how it should be sacred and kept behind locked doors and things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Let's get to your real hero, it's Bruce Springsteen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce Springsteen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce Springsteen"]}, "docId": "120803pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "It's your dream to do a duet with the boss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "There are two American artists that I would love to work with, Bruce Springsteen and Elmo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]